lollipop-network.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy and cookies

**Lollipop’s Priavacy Policy and Cookies**

**1\. The inclusion of personal data in the files of LOLLIPOP NETWORK, S.L.:**

Pursuant to the provisions of Organic Law 15/1999, of 13 December, governing the Protection of Personal Data, all such information the User provides through online web forms of the Website shall be collected and processed in files owned by LOLLIPOP NETWORK, S.L. (hereinafter referred to as “the Company”) for the purposes of providing the services requested by the User, replying to their requests and keeping the User informed of the products and services marketed by the Company, including by way of electronic means. If you do not wish to receive this type of electronic correspondence (e-mails), you may so indicate by ticking the boxes provided for that purpose, or by sending an e-mail to legal@lollipop-network.com. The completion of all information marked as mandatory on this Website is necessary in order to ensure optimum provision of the services offered to the User. If this data is not provided, the Company does not guarantee that the information and services requested may be offered, correctly supplied or meet the needs of the User. The Company informs that it has implemented security measures of a technical and organizational measure to ensure the security of the user’s personal data and avoid its alteration, loss, and / or unauthorized access, given the state of technology the nature of the data stored and the risks they are exposed, whether from human action or the physical or natural environment.

**2\. Submission of data for staff selection:**

Curriculum vitaes submitted by the User to the Company will be used for the sole purpose of responding to applications for employment related to jobs advertised. By providing your personal information, you acknowledge that the data provided is yours and is accurate and true.

**3\. Prohibition on registration by minors:**

Persons under the age of 14 must obtain prior consent from their parents or guardians before providing their personal information to the Company. If you are a minor, please ask your parents or guardians to contact us first.

**4\. Third Party disclosure:**

Lollipop does not collect any personal identifiable data, and any statement otherwise must be considered as false.

**5\. Exercise of rights:**

The User may exercise their rights to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by sending an e-mail to legal@lollipop-network.com or by writing to the Company, Calle Diputación 237, 5º 4ª, 08007 Barcelona (España). In either case, the user must send a copy of his/ her identity card, passport or other valid form of identification.

**6\. Communication of information by the User:**

Before providing personal information belonging to third parties, the User must obtain their prior express consent and inform the parties concerned of the terms of this Privacy Policy. The User undertakes to not hold the Company liable for any possible claim, fine or penalty it may be obliged to bear as a result of the User’s breach of the obligations set forth in this clause.

**7\. Cookies:**

Lollipop Network, S.L. may use cookies either directly or through third parties for the provision of measurement services when the User accesses the Website. Cookies are files sent to the browser from a web server to record the User’s activities on the Website. The cookies used by the Website are solely associated with an anonymous user and their computer, and do not provide any personal information regarding the User. Through the use of cookies, the server hosting the Website may recognize the browser used by the User in order to make web browsing simpler, allowing, for example, and if applicable, access for users who have previously registered to areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively for users without having to register every time they visit the Website. Cookies are also used to measure website audience and traffic parameters and to monitor the progress and number of visits. The User can also change the settings on their browser in order to receive a notice of the receipt of cookies and to prevent the installation of cookies on their device. Please refer to your web browser’s instructions for further information. To use this Website, the user does not have to allow the installation of cookies sent by the Website or third parties acting on behalf of Lollipop Network, S.L.; however, the User, if applicable, may have to log in each time for those services requiring previous registration or “login”.

**8\. Lollipop’s cookies:**

By using the Website and the Lollipop application, the user acknowledges and accepts that the Software may install cookies from Lollipop Network, S.L., as well as cookies by Videology Ltd. and Google Inc. The user can consult Videology Ltd.’s privacy policy by clicking the following link: <http://www.videologygroup.com/index.php/es/menu-privacy-policy.html>, as well as Google Inc’s privacy policy: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). The cookies used by Aedge Performance BCN, S.L.U. serve their purpose to personalize the advertisements and offers that the user receives based on the URL’s he/she visits, as well as the user’s web search. The user is able to configure their browser at any time to not accept cookies. More information regarding the use of cookies is available at [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.>
